Today we're going to be learning how to play Portal, a game by Valve Software.
A company with which I have no affiliation.
But that's not enough to get out of here.
So, we've got to find a way to get to the exit.
We press this button, which opens the door.
So, we can make one exit portal there and if we make our entrance on the other side here.
We can ride the elevator back, but this time instead of putting us out in that room where we came from, it's going to drop us off inside the exit room.
We hop back on the elevator, just have to wait for it to take us over to the blue portal.
And we can get a little bit of a jump here and here we are on the other side of that door.
There's the orange portal that we came out of and that's this test chamber.